# Hasini Sewwandi Dumankorala



Maharanugegoda, 11850 Kadawatha, Sri Lanka

+94766760943 🚗 N9727015

Sri Lankan Single

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/hasini-sewwandi-8031a2214/

# **Objectives**

To build up experience and expand my knowledge. Being organized in a challenging environment to make my skills successful, while offering to make use of my educational, professional & social experience to mutually attain employer's objectives & my objectives.

### **Skills**

Effective interpersonal & communication skills & positive thinking

Advanced knowledge on MS Office package

Advanced knowledge on internet and website

Leadership Qualities

Time management

# Strengths

Flexibility and Adaptability

**Decision Making Ability** 

Strong analytical, logical and mathematical Skills

**Positive Attitude** 

Ability of clarifying the doubts

#### **Education**

**Bachelor of Business Management (Special) Degree in Finance,** *University of Kelaniya* □ 02/2019 - 02/2023

Successfully completed a Bachelor of Business Management (Special) Degree in Finance with first class offered by the Department of Finance, Faculty of Commerce and Management Studies.

- Dean's List for two years (2017/2018 & 2018/2019)
- Cumulative GPA 3.83

# Corporate Level, Chartered Accountants,

Institute of Chartered Accountants of Sri Lanka ☑

09/2017 - present

Following Charted Accountants - Corporate Level

# ICT Technician Course (NVQ level IV),

**NESEC Vocational Training Center** 01/2018 - 06/2018

Successfully completed Information Communication Technology Technician course - NVQ level IV in NESEC Vocational Training Center

#### Advancing Career Skills (English) course,

Technical College – Gampaha 09/2017 - 12/2017

Successfully completed Advancing Career Skills (English) course in Technical College -Gampaha

### Association of Accounting Technicians (AAT),

Association of Accounting Technicians of Sri Lanka ☑

01/2015 - 06/2016

Successfully completed Association of Accounting Technicians of Sri Lanka (AAT) Final in July 2016

# G.C.E (Advanced Level) Examination - 2017,

Viharamahadevi Balika Vidyalaya -

Kiribathqoda 🛮

Z score - 1.6970 Index Number - 5463246

Accounting **Business Studies A** Economics Α General English C

# G.C.E. Ordinary Level Examination - 2014,

Viharamahadevi Balika Vidyalaya -

Kiribathqoda ♂

Five A passes, Three B passes, One C pass

# **Professional Experience**

**QST Lanka (Pvt) Ltd,** *Finance Executive* ☑ 06/2023 – present | Colombo 08, Sri Lanka

- Maintaining accurate records of financial transactions according to Generally Accepted Accounting Principles.
- Creating monthly SVAT schedules and upload to the RAMIS.
- Creating ad hoc reports as requested by executive management team members.
- Managing accounts payable and receivable functions to ensure timely payments of invoices and collections of receivables ABSS Premier (MYOB).
- Establishing internal controls over accounting processes to ensure accuracy in reporting results.
- Providing oversight of the company's capital structure by monitoring debt levels and ensuring sufficient liquidity is available for operations.

# Transworld Logistics Lanka (Pvt) Ltd.

Executive - Finance

12/2022 - present | Colombo 08

- Budgeting /planning and cash flow management of the company and handling account payables and account receivables (both LKR & USD).
- Following up debtors and creditors and bank reconciliations.
- Handling petty cash process and IOU.
- Assisting with annual budgeting external audit requirement, month end closure, report preparation, analysis and reporting for management, cash flow forecast statement on payments.
- Preparing and uploading of month end journal entries to Oracle Fusion.

# Finance Intern

11/2021 – 11/2022 | Colombo 08

- Proficiency in Microsoft Office applications like Microsoft Excel, Word, and PowerPoint and proficiency using Oracle Fusion.
- Multitasking in order to successfully handle multiple accounts (Payable and Receivable).
- Monitor all banking activities in order to detect irregularities & prepare monthly bank reconciliation reports regarding all cash deposits to the bank.
- Tracking organization expenses (office rent, insurance, office supplies etc.)
- Processing container deposit refunds and maintaining a refund payable schedule. Working with collection agencies on overdue payments.
- Performing clerical and interoffice support, including mail receipt and processing.

# **Volunteer Experience**

# Leo Club of University of Kelaniya,

Member ☑ 2019 – present

#### References

Mr. L. A. S. Perera, Lecturer (Probationary), University of Kelaniya shanakala@kln.ac.lk, 0713661932

#### Mrs. S. S. Mallikarachchi.

Electrical Superintendent, Ceylon Electricity Board 324, Kandy Road, Eldeniya, Kadawatha. sagarikasm86@gmail.com, 071 406 6321

Mrs. B. A. K. G. Nadeeshika, Design Engineer, Alcobronz Engineering Pvt. Ltd., No. 130/6, Major Wasantha Gunarathna Mw., Mahara, Kadawatha.

mailto:gnadeeshika@gmail.com, 077 230 5779 / 071 014 8266

### **Declaration**

I hereby declare that the above particulars of facts and information stated are true, correct and complete to the best of my belief and knowledge.

Hasini Sewwandi Dumankorala

Menneroli